In this video we're going to continue and complete our discussion of cool
在这段视频中，我们将继续并完成对COOL的讨论
operational semantics. We'll be taking a look with the two most complex operations
操作语义学。我们将通过两个最复杂的操作来看一看
in cool, the allocation of the new object and dynamic dispatch. We'll begin by
在COOL中，新对象的分配和动态调度。我们将从
giving an informal discussion of what happens when a new object is allocated in
中分配新对象时会发生什么的非正式讨论
Kuhl. So, the first thing that has to happen, if we have to allocate space for
库尔。所以，首先要做的是，如果我们必须为
the object and essentially, that means having enough space for the object
对象，本质上，这意味着要有足够的空间容纳对象
attributes. We're going to have to allocate a location for every attribute of
属性。我们将不得不为每个属性分配一个位置
the object of class t if what we're doing is allocating a new t object. Then we're
类t的对象，如果我们正在做的是分配一个新的t对象。那我们就是
going to set the attributes of, of that object to their default values and well in
将该对象的、的属性设置为其默认值
a few minutes, we'll see what the default values are and why we need to set the, set
几分钟后，我们将看到默认值是什么，以及为什么需要设置、设置
the attributes to defaults. And then we evaluate the initializers so every
要默认的属性。然后我们评估初始值设定项，因此每个
attribute in the class declaration can have an initializing expression. We're
属性可以具有初始化表达式。我们是
going to evaluate those and set the resulting attribute values And then we
对这些进行求值并设置结果属性值，然后我们
return the newly allocated objects. So these are the steps that are involved in
返回新分配的对象。因此，这些都是涉及到的步骤
setting a new object and as you can see it's actually more than just allocating a
设置一个新对象，如您所见，它实际上不仅仅是分配一个
little bit of memory. It's actually quite a bit of computation going on in
一点内存。这实际上是相当大的计算量
allocating new objects in cool. Every class has a default value associated with
在凉爽状态下分配新对象。每个类都有一个与
that class. So for integers, the default value is zero. For Boolean, the default
那节课。因此，对于整数，默认值为零。对于布尔型，默认设置为
value is a Boolean false and for strings, the default value is the empty string And
值为布尔值FALSE，并且对于字符串，默认值为空字符串，并且
then for any other class, that isn't one of these three basic classes or any other
那么对于任何其他类，这不是这三个基本类中的一个，也不是任何其他类
class, the default value is void. In the operational rules, we're going to need a
类，则默认值为void。在操作规则中，我们需要一个
way to repair to the attributes of a class. So we're going to define a function
修复到类的属性的方法。所以我们要定义一个函数
called class that takes a class name and returns the list of attributes of, of that
调用的类，它接受类名并返回、的属性列表
class. So here we have all the attributes of class a, let's say that a1 through and
班级。这里我们有a类的所有属性，让我们假设A1到AND
in addition, this functions also going to tell us for each attribute declared type
此外，此函数还将告诉我们声明的每个属性的类型
of the attribute and the expression that initiali zes the attribute. And one other
属性和初始化该属性的表达式的。和另一个
important feature of this list, is that it includes all the attributes of class a
这个列表的一个重要特征是它包含a类的所有属性
including the inherited ones. And there's another detail which is in what order
包括遗传的。还有一个细节是按什么顺序排列的
these attributes appear and these are actually become important when we define
这些属性会出现，当我们定义以下属性时，这些属性实际上会变得很重要
the semantics of how attributes are initialized and the rule is the attributes
属性如何初始化的语义，规则是属性
are listed in greatest ancestor first order And what do I mean by that? Let's
以最伟大的祖先第一顺序列出，我这是什么意思？我们走吧
say that we have three classes a, b, and c and a, I'm sorry, b inherits from a. And c
假设我们有三个类a、b和c，对不起，b继承自a和c
inherits. From b. Okay, let's say, that a defines two attributes, a1 and a2 and b
继承。好的，假设a定义了两个属性，a1、a2和b
defines two attributes b1, b2 and c defines two attributes c1 and c2. Then
定义两个属性b1、b2和c定义两个属性c1和c2。然后
class of c. We'll list the attributes in the following order. First we'll come a1
类。我们将按以下顺序列出属性。我们先走A1路
and then a2 Because a is the greatest ancestor, okay, it's the, the closest to
然后是a2，因为a是最伟大的祖先，好的，它是最接近
the root of the object hierarchy and the attribute was in class a or within any
对象层次结构的根和属性在a类中或在任何
class, it's always listed in the order that it textually appear. So, first comes
类中，它始终以文本形式出现的顺序列出。所以，首先来的是
a1 and a2 and of course the type in the initializer are also, let's see here, most
a1和a2，当然还有初始化式中的类型也是，让我们在这里看到，大多数
of these attributes but we're just concentrating here in the order in which
这些属性，但我们在这里集中讨论的顺序是
the information appears. So, the next would come class b. So, the attributes of
此时将显示该信息。因此，下一个是类b。所以，
class b will be next and of course, there'll be the type and initialize for
接下来是类b，当然还有类型和初始化
those attributes and then finally the attributes of class c Again, in the order
这些属性，最后是类c的属性，按如下顺序
in which they are listed in the class definition, okay? So, that defines the
将它们列在类定义中，好吗？因此，这定义了
order of the attributes for any class. It's always in the order of the greatest
任何类的属性顺序。它总是按照最伟大的顺序排列
ancestor down the inheritance chain to the class itself which is the argument of the
沿继承链向下传递到类本身的祖先，这是
class functions. At this point we're ready to actually define the formal semantics of
类函数。此时，我们已经准备好实际定义
new t and let switch colors here. So we're going to be allocating a new object of
新设置，让您在这里切换颜色。所以我们将分配一个新的对象
type and is going to be in a context with self object as zero environment e and
类型，并且将位于自身对象为零的环境e的上下文中，并且
store s. The first thing we have to do we're going to figure out what kind of
我们要做的第一件事就是找出
object it is that we're actually going to allocate and the only question is whether
对象是我们实际上要分配，唯一的问题是
t is se lf type or not because remember self type is not the name of an actual
t是否为se lf类型，因为记住自身类型不是实际类型的名称
class. If t is not self type then the class that we're going to allocate is
班级。如果t不是self类型，那么我们要分配的类是
actually a t. T is actually a class name and with that, that's the kind of object
实际上，t.t实际上是一个类名，有了这个名称，它就是这样一种对象
that we're going to allocate. If t is self type then the kind of object we're going
我们要分配的。如果t是Self类型，那么我们将要使用的对象类型
to be allocating. Is whatever the class is of the self objects? So we're going to
来分配。类是自我对象吗？所以我们要去
look at the dynamic type here of the self object called that x and that will be the
请看这里名为x的self对象的动态类型，它将是
class that we create. That will be the kind of objects that we created, all
我们创建的类。这将是我们创建的那种对象，所有
right? So there's two possibilities, Either object, object, allocating an
对吗？所以有两种可能性，要么是对象，要么是对象，分配一个
object of type t if t is actually a class name. Otherwise it's an object of the same
如果t实际上是一个类名，则类型为t的对象。否则它就是相同的对象
dynamic type as the self object Alright? So, now we're going to look up t0 is,
动态类型作为自我对象，好吗？所以，现在我们来看一下0是，
alright. And we get out the list of the attribute types and initializers for t0.
好的。我们得到t0的属性类型和初始值设定项的列表。
So, this tells that what we have to do to construct an object of this type. Alright
所以，这告诉我们，要构造这种类型的对象，我们必须做些什么。好的，好的
and the next thing we do is we allocate locations for each of the attributes. So,
接下来我们要做的是为每个属性分配位置。所以,
because they were in attributes, we're going to allocate n locations. One for
因为它们在属性中，所以我们将分配n个位置。一张是
each attribute, all right. And then we're going to create an object with the class
每个属性，好的。然后我们将使用类创建一个对象
tag t0 and the attributes are going to be bound to these new locations. So, the i
标签t0和属性将被绑定到这些新位置。所以，我
attribute will be abound to the i new location that we just allocated and that
属性将丰富到我们刚刚分配的i个新位置，并且
were going to update the store. Okay. So, we're going to take our initial store and
我们要更新商店。好吧。所以，我们要把我们的第一家店铺
know this is the same with the store we started with. We take s and we are going
我知道这和我们刚开始开的那家店是一样的。我们坐%s，我们要走了
to update it so that at these new locations, those new locations hold the
为了更新它，以便在这些新位置，这些新位置保存
default values of, for the type of each of the attribute. Okay, and that gives us the
的默认值，表示每个属性的类型。好的，这给了我们
store s1 and now we have to evaluate the initializer. The two actually, initialize
存储s1，现在我们必须计算初始值设定项。这两个实际上是初始化
the attributes. And we have to think about what the environment is in which those
属性。我们必须想一想环境是什么，在这个环境中，
attributes are initialized and remember the rule is that within initializer I
属性已初始化，请记住，规则是在初始化式i中
mean, attribute, all the attributes of the class are in scope. Alright, so the
均值、属性、类的所有属性都在作用域内。好的，所以
environment in this case for the initializers will ju st consist of the
在本例中，初始化器的环境将由
initializer or the attributes, excuse me, themselves. Okay, so these are the
初始值设定项或属性，抱歉，它们本身。好的，这些是
attribute names and the i attributes is bound to the i's new memory location
属性名和I属性被绑定到I的新内存位置
holding the value, the default value initially of that attribute. Alright, and
保存该值，即该属性的初始默认值。好的，还有
then finally, to evaluate initializers, we just evaluate them as a block in the order
最后，为了评估初始值设定项，我们只需按顺序将它们评估为挡路
which they appear in the class function. This is why it was important to specify
它们出现在类函数中。这就是为什么指定
the order in the class function. So remember that these attributes include all
类函数中的顺序。因此请记住，这些属性包括所有
the inherited attribute so we'll start by evaluating initializing attributes with
继承的属性，因此我们将从评估初始化属性开始
the greatest ancestor and working our way down to the attributes declared within the
最伟大的祖先，一直到
class itself. Notice that the environment here. Which has all of the attributes in
类本身。注意这里的环境。它具有中的所有属性
scope is an interesting point, this environment has nothing to do with the
范围是一个有趣的问题，这个环境与
environment in which new t is actually evaluation. You know, these environments e
实际评估新测试的环境。你知道，这些环境
and e prime are completely separate, okay? So new, so e prime has in scope the names
和e质数是完全分开的，好吗？所以很新，所以e一号在范围内有名字
of the attributes the class e is a, you know, is, is some other environment.
在e类的属性中，你知道，是，是一些其他的环境。
There's some functions somewhere that's calling new t and the variables are in
有一些函数正在调用new t，变量在
scope there are just completely different, okay? But anyway, evaluating this block Of
范围是完全不同的，好吗？但不管怎样，评估这个挡路
initializers will yield some value. And the new store the value isn't used for
初始值设定项将产生一些值。以及该值不用于的新存储
anything, okay? But the new store is the final store. That's the store that we get
什么都行，好吗？但是新店是最后一家店。那就是我们买到的那家店
out as a result of allocating the object and then what is the result of new t, well
作为分配对象的结果，那么新t的结果是什么？
it is the new object itself, v. To summarize the semantics of New that was
这是新对象本身，v。总结一下New的语义
the first three steps allocate the object, actually allocate the memory
前三个步骤分配对象，实际分配内存
for the object and then the remaining steps initialize the objects by evaluating
，然后其余步骤通过计算
a sequence of assignments and the most important thing probably to understand
一系列作业和最重要的可能要理解的事情
about initialization and one of the most important things is the context in which
关于初始化，最重要的事情之一是
or the stage in which the initializers are evaluated. So know that only the attribute
或评估初始化器的阶段。所以要知道，只有属性
are in scope while we emphasize that and it's the same rule as of typing. So when
是在范围内的，我们强调这一点，这和打字的规则是一样的。那么什么时候
you 're type checking a class declaration only the attributes are in scope of the
您正在对类声明进行类型检查，只有属性在
you know, for the initializers of the class and then as the same, naturally the
您知道，对于类的初始值设定项，然后是相同的，自然
same thing that we use when we actually evaluate the initializers at runtime. And
与我们在运行时实际计算初始值设定项时使用的内容相同。和
the initial values of the attributes are the default values and then, then we need
属性的初始值是默认值，然后，我们需要
the defaults because, precisely because the attributes are in-sculpt inside their
缺省值是因为，正是因为属性在其
own initializers. So, it could be for example, it's perfectly reasonable like
拥有初始值设定项。所以，它可能是，举个例子，它非常合理，就像
Kuhls to have an initializer, let's say, like this. And I'm just going to, I may
库尔斯有一个初始化器，比方说，像这样。我正要去，我可能会
leave all the types here just to save time but I can assign and attribute a the value
为了节省时间，将所有类型都留在这里，但我可以为值赋值并赋值
of a and this is perfectly okay because the right hand side of the intializer has
这是完全没有问题的，因为初始化式的右手边有
all the attributes and scope and for this to make sense a has to have some kind of
所有的属性和作用域，要想理解这一点，a必须有某种
default value. It has to have some initial value so because I might read it, before I
默认值。它必须有一些初始值，因为我可能会读到它，在我
might read an attribute before I have actually finished computing its
可能会在我实际完成属性的计算之前读取该属性
initializer All right? And the last point here, is that notice that in the
初始化器可以吗？这里的最后一点是，请注意，在
initialization or in the yeah, in the initialization of an object self is the
初始化还是在初始化是的，在初始化一个对象本身就是
object itself is the self object. And what do I mean by that? I forgot to mention
对象本身就是自我对象。我这么说是什么意思？我忘了说了
this on the previous slide just flipping back to that slide for a moment, notice
请注意，上一张幻灯片上的内容只是暂时返回到那张幻灯片
here. That in the evaluation of the initializers, what is the context the self
这里。在对初始化器的评价中，自我的语境是什么
object is v, the self object is v, this is the new object that we have just
对象是v，自我对象是v，这是我们刚刚拥有的新对象
constructed. And so, it's perfectly fine for e1 or en, the initialization
建造的。因此，对于e1或en，初始化是完全合适的
expressions over here and refers to stealth and what they were referred to if
表达式在这里，并且指的是隐形，以及在以下情况下它们被指的是什么
they use self is the object that is being initialized. Alright Returning to this, to
它们使用Self是正在初始化的对象。好了，回到这个，到
our summary you know it might be a little bit of a surprise how complicated the.
我们的总结，你知道，这可能会让人有点惊讶，它是多么的复杂。
Semantics of new is, in cool and it's not just cool that has that property. In fact
new的语义是，在Cool中，并不是只有Cool才有这个属性。事实上
every object oriented language, language has a fairly complex semantics for the
每种面向对象的语言，语言都有相当复杂的语义
initialization of new objects and it's a combination of features like inheritance
初始化新对象，它是继承等功能的组合
and the ability of initializers to refer to the attributes that leads to this kind
以及初始化器引用导致这种类型的属性的能力
of complexity. Now let's talk about the semantics of dynamic dispatch and we'll
是复杂的。现在让我们讨论一下动态分派的语义，我们将
follow the same plan that we did the semantics of new for us giving for us have
遵循与我们为我们提供的new的语义相同的计划
an informal discussion and high level description of how the evaluation of
非正式讨论和高层次描述如何评价
dynamic dispatch works and then we'll look at the formal operational rule. So the
动态分派是有效的，然后我们将查看正式的操作规则。因此，
first thing it happens in evaluating a dispatch is that we'll evaluate the
评估派单时发生的第一件事是，我们将评估
arguments e1 through en and next we'll evaluate the target object e0 so that
参数e1到en，接下来我们将计算目标对象e0，以便
expression to get the actual object to which we're dispatching. Next, we're going
表达式来获取我们要调度到的实际对象。接下来，我们要去
to look at the dynamic type of the target object. So, after we evaluate the zero,
若要查看目标对象的动态类型，请执行以下操作。所以，在我们评估完零之后，
we're going to look at its class peg is And then, we're going to use that type to
我们将查看它的类关联，然后，我们将使用该类型
figure out which function which function f we're supposed to use. So, we're going to
找出我们应该使用哪个函数。所以，我们要去
go and look in the method table for the class x and see what method it has for f.
转到方法表中查找类x，看看它对f有什么方法。
Then we're going to create new locations and an environment for the call. Alright, and
然后，我们将为电话会议创建新的地点和环境。好的，还有
we're going to set up a new locations for the actual parameters. We're going to
我们将为实际参数设置一个新位置。我们要去
initialize the, those locations with the actual arguments. Where s itself to be the
使用实际参数初始化这些位置。它本身应该在哪里呢？
target object and then we're going to evaluate the body of f. Now in order to do
目标对象，然后我们将计算f的主体。现在为了
the look up of a method in a class, we're going to need some representation of what
在类中查找方法时，我们将需要一些表示
methods exist and which class is in our operational rules. So we're going to find
方法存在，以及我们的操作规则中包含哪个类。所以我们要找出
a function eval stands for implementation and the implementation in a class a of a
函数eval代表实现以及
method f is, is going to be first of all, the list of formal parameters. So it's
方法f是，首先是形式参数列表。所以这就是
going to tell us what the formal parameters are of f and then the body of f
告诉我们f的形式参数是什么，然后是f的主体
Whatever the, the function body of f is. Now we're ready to actually discuss the
不管是什么，f的函数体是。现在我们准备好实际讨论
details of the formal operational semantics of method dispatch in Kuhl. I'm
Kuhl中方法分派的形式化操作语义的详细信息。我
going to switch colors here again just for contrast. So as we said, the first thing
我要在这里再换一次颜色，只是为了对比一下。所以就像我们说的，第一件事
we do is we evaluate the n arguments. So this first in lines, take care of that ad
我们要做的就是评估这n个论点。所以这是第一行，注意那个广告
notice that each arguments that's evaluated may have side effects. So, it
请注意，评估的每个参数都可能有副作用。所以，它
starts in some store but it may produce a different store. So after we've done all
从一些商店开始，但可能会产生不同的商店。所以在我们做完所有的事情之后
of this we'll have the n arguments evaluated and some store s (N). The next
其中，我们将计算n个参数，并存储s(N)。下一个
thing that happens is we evaluate zero. This is the expression to which we are
发生的事情是我们评估为零。这就是我们要表达的意思
dispatching and that would give us an object v0 and some updated store s (n) +
调度，这将给我们一个对象V0和一些更新的存储s(N)+
one. Okay And now we have to inspect v0. We want to know what's inside of v0, what
一。好的，现在我们要检查V0。我们想知道V0里面有什么，
v0 is made of and in particular we're interested in the classed tag of v0 and
V0由我们特别感兴趣的V0的分类标记组成，
we'll also be interested in the contents of its attributes. The locations
我们还将对其属性的内容感兴趣。地点
associated with its attributes but first let's focus on the class tag. Alright,
与其属性相关联，但首先让我们将重点放在类标记上。好的，
because we're going to use that class, remember, this is the dynamic type of the
因为我们将使用该类，请记住，这是
zeros and what kind of objects the zeros actually is when the program is running.
零，以及当程序运行时，零实际上是什么类型的对象。
And we're going to use that class to look up the definition of f that we should run.
我们将使用这个类来查找我们应该运行的f的定义。
So, we look for the method f in class x. We want to know its implementation and in
因此，我们在类x中查找方法f。
particular we get the names of the former parameters. Okay x1 through xn and we get
具体地说，我们得到了以前参数的名称。好的，从x1到xn，我们得到
the body of the function or method. Alright So, the next thing we have to do
函数或方法的主体。好的，接下来我们要做的是
is we have to allocate space in the memory or in the store for the actual parameters
我们必须在内存中还是在存储中为实际参数分配空间
of the method call. So, we allocate new locations. Okay, one for each actual
方法调用的。所以，我们分配新的地点。好的，一人一份
argument and that we're ready to build an environment in which we can evaluate the
我们已经准备好建立一个环境，在这个环境中我们可以评估
method, alright? So, what is this environment going to consist of? So, we
方法，好吗？那么，这个环境将由什么组成呢？所以，我们
have to think about what names or in-scoped inside of a method. Well, all
必须考虑方法中的名称或作用域是什么。嗯，都是
the attributes of the class are in-scope. Okay. So, this is a class x with
类的属性在范围内。好吧。所以，这是一个x类，它有
attributes a1 through an so the environment will have those names to find
属性A1到AN，因此环境将具有要查找的这些名称
a1 through an. And now what are the attributes or locations of those
A1至An。那么现在它们的属性或位置是什么呢？
attributes. Well those are the locations of. The zero, that's the object that we're
属性。这些都是。零，这就是我们的目标
dispatching to that were going to be the self object and the attribute names will
调度到的对象将是Self对象，属性名称将
refer to the attributes of, of self, alright. So, those locations here are the
指的是，自我的属性，好的。那么，这里的那些位置就是
locations of, of the attributes in the object v0. Now in addition the formal
对象V0中属性的位置。现在除了正式的
paramete rs are also in scope inside of the method body. So we add to this
参数r也在方法体内部作用域中。所以我们再加上这个
environment with just the attributes all of the formal parameters okay and they are
仅具有所有形式参数的属性的环境，它们都是
at the new locations l(x1) up to l(xn). Okay? And notice one slight subtlety about
在新位置l(X1)直到l(Xn)。好吧?注意到一个细微的地方，那就是
the way this is defined we're taking an initial environment which I'll show here
按照定义的方式，我们采用的是初始环境，我将在这里展示这一点
with, I'll, I'll color these braces in blue. So we're defining and initial
我会，我会把这些牙套涂成蓝色。所以我们在定义和首字母缩写
environment of the attributes and then we're doing updates to that, okay? So
属性的环境，然后我们会对其进行更新，好吗？所以
we're, instead of just defining x1 to map two l sub x1, we're saying we're replacing
我们不是简单地定义x1来映射两个l/x1，而是说我们正在替换
The definition of x1 in this environment in the blue braces with one and maps x1
此环境中的x1定义在蓝色大括号中加1，并映射x1
and l(x1). Why do we do it that way? Well, the thing is that a method may have a
和l(X1)。我们为什么要那样做呢？嗯，问题是一个方法可能有一个
formal parameter that is the same as an attribute name so for example I could have
与属性名称相同的形参，例如，我可以使用
a class a that has an attribute little a in it And it also has a method f that
一个a类，其中有一个属性小a，并且它也有一个方法f
takes a formal parameter named a. Okay And if I do that, and of course, I'm leaving
接受一个名为a的形参。好的，如果我这样做了，当然，我要离开
out types and lots of other things here. So, here I have an attribute named
我们这里有各种类型和很多其他的东西。因此，这里我有一个名为
a that's declared. And then I have a method that takes the argument
A这是已经宣布的。然后我有一个方法，它接受这个参数
called a. And then the question is when I refer to a. Inside of the body of the
然后问题是，当我引用
method what a do I get? Is this a, is this a bind to the formal parameters, is it
方法我得到的是什么？这是一个，这是对形参的绑定，是吗
bind to the attribute? And the answer, we have to get one answer or the other, the
是否绑定到该属性？而答案，我们必须得到一个或另一个答案，
answer in Kuhl, is that it binds to the formal parameter that hides the, the outer
Kuhl的答案是，它绑定到隐藏外部的形参
name. Okay, and that's, and that's enforced here in the rule by these
名字。好的，这是，这是由这些人在规则中强制执行的
updates. So, if a formal parameter has the same name as one of the attributes, it
更新。因此，如果形式参数与其中一个属性同名，则它
will replace the definition of the attribute in the environment. Okay. Once
将替换环境中的属性定义。好吧。一次
we get the environment set up, we need to set up our store what, what are the
我们把环境设置好了，我们需要开我们的店什么，什么是
changes to the store? What we just have to store the actual value of each argument at
商店有什么变化吗？我们只需将每个参数的实际值存储在
the location for that argument. And finally, we are ready to evaluate the
该参数的位置。最后，我们准备好评估
functioning body and the interesting part here is the context in which that's done.
有功能的身体，这里有趣的部分是做这件事的背景。
So, notice here that the that the self object in, in the context of running the
请注意，在运行
method f is the object to which are dispatching. Okay? And then the
方法f是要调度到的对象。好吧?然后是
environment is e prime, the new environment we just set up and once again
环境是最好的，我们刚刚建立的新环境，一次又一次
notice that this is a complete change of context that e prime, the environment e
请注意，这是上下文的完全改变，即e主，环境e
prime has nothing to do with the environment e. E prime is built completely
素数与环境无关。e素数完全是建立起来的。
from scratch using only information about the method for calling, it doesn't borrow
仅使用有关调用方法的信息从头开始，而不是借用
anything from the, from the environment where the method originated, where the
任何内容，从方法起源的环境，其中
method was called from. And finally all of this is done in the store that has,
方法是从调用的。最后，所有这些都是在商店里完成的，
reflects all the side effects performed by evaluating the arguments, by evaluating e0
通过计算e0反映通过计算参数执行的所有副作用
and by extending the store with the locations for the actual parameters. So to
并通过用实际参数的位置扩展存储。所以要
evaluate the body of the method we get back a value and another updated store and
评估方法体，我们将获得一个值和另一个更新的存储，并
that value in store are the results of the entire execution of the dynamic dispatch.
存储中的值是整个动态分派执行的结果。